Incoming Call
Kitahama-Senpai
Hello...?
Rin? Were you still asleep?
Uh huh...
Sold Out
The movie we were thinking of seeing today...
it looks like it'll be packed.
You want to check out a different one?
I wanna see Angel J.
Say what now?
Angel J...
Angel Jewel The Movie
The Memorial Diamond
Oh, it's an anime.
That's kinda childish, Rin.
It's really cute.
Monika-chan is a jewel thief
who wants to become an idol.
Uh-huh...
And she can shoot a laser cutter
from her left eye.
Say what?!
Now I'm kinda interested.
Why does she want to be an idol?
Hang on, I think I'd be
embarrassed going to see this.
Any other options?
I dunno how to interpret
those puppy sounds...
Ayaka wants to see Angel J...
Pardon me, I think I've got
the wrong person.
Ayaka-chan, where's your sister?
Sleeping right next to me.
Could you put her...
Actually, could you
describe what she looks like?
Let's see...
Her hair's like the sun. All exploded.
Exploded? I wanna see!
Also, her tummy is out.
I really... actually, could you cover it up?
So she doesn't get sick.
Are you two going out today?
Yep, there was a movie she wanted to see.
I wish I could see Angel J...
I don't think that was it...
You wanna come with us?
Since I've got you on the line.
Episode 11                       Love Triangle?
Y'know, during summer vacation,
I secretly got my licen—
Senpai, you dumped me.
I've got my heart set
on one girl, right now.
I'm not gonna make eyes
at you or Imp-chan anymore!
I'm gonna get serious from now on!
You realize I was talking about
Spoiled-chan and the characters, right?
I didn't dump you, Rin!
After all this time, they're a part of me!
But it was your birthday,
and I wanted you to have a good time...
I put it on every morning with a grin.
Your words and your expression
are not matching!
I haven't given up, you know...
I'm going to make you fall
with my acting someday!
Into hell?
Anyway... during summer vacation,
I got my license in secret.
You wanna go shopping someday?
I extremely want to.
But your face!
You seem different, somehow.
Did you forget the face
of the girl you love?
Wait... Imp-chan?
Are we going to be doing this all day?
Who knows if it'll end after only today.
You really hold a grudge.
But since I announced my
intention to get serious,
I won't let you wrap me around your finger!
And I'm begging you, please don't
mess with me while I'm driving!
Let's roll out!
Seriously, it's dangerous!
You're making me want to
see you act silly, Senpai...
Come on.
If it keeps you safe, I'll act like
an absolute buffoon, but not right now.
What's wrong?
Nothing...
Oh, it looks like Kitahama
has scored the first point!
Th-The game has just begun!
You're being awfully quiet, Imp-chan.
Yeah... I think I'm carsick.
Seriously? Because of my driving?
We're almost there, so open up the window
and try to look at something in the distance.
Nope.
I wanna look at your face
while you focus on driving.
Hey, did that make your heart skip a beat?
...Are you actually carsick?
A little.
She can act even when
she's not feeling well.
Gotta say, vulnerable Imp-chan
is kind of awesome...
Wait, is it all acting?!
I can't even tell anymore!
Here, we're at the ocean.
Hey, you aren't looking
at the water are you?
The ocean looks cool.
Is that really Rin sitting
beside me right now?!
What's wrong?
Well, it really feels like
a really feminine space...
Well, I'm gonna try this on.
You're leaving me alone?!
I don't know what to do
with you when you're so clingy.
Imp-chan's set the pace...
What kind of fashion sense
do you like on a girl, Senpai?
I don't really know fashion.
If you bring some clothes
you like, I'll try them on.
A sister...
You want me to cosplay for you?
You said I could bring what I like!
I put it on!
Let's see.
I-I put this on so that I could
make you fall for me, got it?!
Tsundere-chan?!
You wanted to come here?
I love how they sell
whole sets of furniture!
This sofa is super soft!
You're making such a big deal. So childish.
I'm serious! Try it out.
If you insist, I guess.
Oh, this really is comfortable.
Huh, I would've figured
Tsundere-chan would be more like...
Well... I guess it's fine.
I-it'd be nice if we could sit
here like this and enjoy drinks...
I-I guess it's strange... me
saying how I really feel.
Th-This was so stupid.
There was no way... I could pull it off.
That was the dere part of the tsundere!
I have to stay strong!
Use your head, dang it!
I have to give a clever r-r-response!
Hey, hey!
Multi-Purpose Sofa
I don't think we should be
sitting here for too long.
Everybody panic!
Pseudo Harem
Would've been nicer to hit
the beach during the summer, huh?
Whoa, whoa!
You die if you get wet.
Should we fight to the death then?
Obviously not.
Hey, wait!
Stop that!
The waves are getting closer!
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
Here it comes, here it comes...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
W-What're you acting so childish for?
W-Whoa there!
Nobody's dead yet.
Are you really feeling that competitive?
I-I wouldn't say that's...
Oh no!
Are you okay, Rin?
So.. so...
If I catch a cold after this,
I'm making sure you have it too!
Should we be bantering when you're soaked?!
And... did my bracelet get wet?
Oh, no, I think it's fine.
But I'm more worried about you, Rin.
But what about me?
I knew it.
It's not like you gave
the bracelet to me...
But I couldn't bring myself
to take it off today.
Because... I like you just as much.
This isn't just acting anymore, is it?
I thought only paying special attention
to Rin would show how serious I was.
But...
I was wrong.
I love every version of Rin.
I got Senpai to fall for me!
I might be soaking,
but is it okay if I hug you?!
You already are!
It's cold! We're gonna get sick!
That's what I warned you about!
I wanna see what it feels like
when you go really fast.
Let's cruise Shuto Expressway at night.
Maybe if you wanna catch a cold.
How are you most excited
about going home...?
Because I like being able to make you weak
in the knees with my acting.
Well, let's drive home
at a nice, safe speed.
I don't want to go home tod—
Here, warm up some.
For the next date,
it's Cool-chan's turn, okay?
You're gonna act the entire time again?!
Maybe an aquarium or a zoo.
What about a haunted house?
No way!
Or maybe we could re-do everything
from today for Cool-chan.
I have to take every different
character through the same date?!
That'd mean seeing
the same movie five times, huh?
...That'd be the hardest for me.
You realized that, huh?
I have to assume acting
all day can't be easy.
I am exhausted...
I guess I'll have to take some time off.
Feel free to sleep on the way back.
That seems like such a waste!
Besides, I feel like I'll really
catch a cold if I fall asleep.
Put this on.
Unless you want your body to be Cool-chan?
Now I really am gonna get sick!
Good morning, Mr. Driver.
I've come to pick you up, ladies.
Hup...
Ayaka-chan, which way to your school?
You can see it over there.
That is not the kind of distance
a drive is necessary for, milady.
Put on some music!
I've got a song from that anime you like.
Track Name: Angel Heart <3
Artist: Monika
Album: Anime [Angel Jewel] Best Album
When the moon is full, and the stars shine!
When my heartstrings are plucked,
there's magic in the night sky!
Emeralds, looking you in the eye!
Feelings, like sapphires, unchanging...
We're here, milady.
Can I sing all the way to the end?
Sure.
Oh, you're spoiling her!
I'm sure, we'll get, more. Go!
The stars will rain down...
I can't hear you, miss.
Singing in front of people is...
Even though you sing lots at home.
Aya!
You'll understand how inadequate
your singing is too, some day!
Oh, there's Moe-chan.
Thanks, Mr. Driver, I'm gonna go.
Be safe!
Aya!
You've got the same blood
flowing in your veins too, y'know!
Bye bye, onee-chan!
I'd like to hear you sing someday, Rin.
I guess I better practice then...
All right! Something to look forward to.
Or maybe we should drive straight
to a karaoke place?
What?
Then I can oversee your practice!
No way!
Too bad, I'm in control
of our destination!
I'm being kidnapped!
Short Stories
About Falling In Love
Now accepting
submissions!
A short film about falling in love?
Yeah, I wanna enter this thing!
And I'm gonna need your help, Eiji!
Okay, but...
do you have any idea how to make a movie?
I've got it covered!
I'm gonna direct and
I've already got all the gear!
Huh, talk about initiative.
The others from the club
have already agreed to help!
So is the only thing left to film it?
I've got... no ideas for story.
Well, that seems important.
Romance plots, huh...
Why not get some advice
from someone in the club?
I am a writer first, director second!
How would that look?!
Your pride won't stand for it, I get that.
Maybe ask someone
with a girlfriend for input?
That'd work too, yep.
I'm not expecting much here...
Are there any stories you can tell us about
Nanakura-san that might be good reference?
Very well, let me enlighten you.
It was a few days ago,
when the weather was neither
particularly good or bad, hot or cold...
So, no, then?
Nailed it.
You'll need to ask her about
the romantic side of things!
Then put her in touch with me.
Tsuu-chan, you don't
have Rin's contact info?
Even though I do?
Come on, it's embarrassing
to ask a girl for that stuff.
And this is the guy who wants
to do a romance flick?!
Discovering New Stars
Kitahama-Senpai
Hello! This is Rin.
Okay... okay.
Sure.
Right! I'll do it.
You scared me there!
Oh, sorry.
So, I'll let him know you said okay.
Right.
The thing with Tsuu-chan, though...
he's got no cool when it comes to girls.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
Right. Good night.
Documentary: Much Ado About Nothing X
Documentary Much Ado About Nothing X!
Q. What do you do
on your days off?
I sleep all the way until noon.
So much rest... my head's all loopy.
That, or my hobby,
which is playing video games.
I play for hours on end...
until my head's all loopy.
What does a
stage represent
to Kitahama Eiji?
Probably seedless grapes that
are so good you can eat them, skin included.
They get rid of the only downside
to eating grapes, which was the seeds!
It's nothing short of revolutionary!
Hey, peaches! You're shaking
in your boots, right?!
Hey, answer me! Peaches!
You've been supplanted in this,
the age of the seedless grape! Got that?!
What is he doing?
Don't ask me.